Guide to the Clive L. DuVal papers, 1960-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1973-1994
  - General Correspondence, pt 1, October 1989 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, pt 2, October 1989 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, pt 1, November 1989 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, pt 2, November 1989 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - State Agencies, 1972-1974 (Box 161, Folder 30)
  - CLD Correspondence, January 1991 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - CLD Correspondence, December 1990 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - CLD, December 1990 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, November 1990 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, October 1990 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, August 1990 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, September 1990 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, November 1991 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, October 1991 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, October 1991 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, July 1991 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, August 1991 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, January 1992 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, July-December 1992 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, January-July 1993 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, July-December 1993 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, January-June 1994 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, July-December 1994 (Box 172, Folder 17)
  - Topical Correspondence: Constituents' Letters, pt 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Topical Correspondence: Constituents' Letters, pt 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Topical Correspondence: Recommendations, pt 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Topical Correspondence: Recommendations, pt 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Topical Correspondence: Letters of Congratulations (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Topical Correspondence: Thank You Letters to Volunteers and Names (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Topical Correspondence: Club View Drive (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Topical Correspondence: Environmental Protection Agency Article (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Topical Correspondence: Erol's Inc. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Topical Correspondence: Great Falls Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Store (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Topical Correspondence: Great Falls Street, 1966-1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Topical Correspondence: Great Falls Street, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Topical Correspondence: Great Falls Street, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Topical Correspondence: Historic Landmarks / Supreme Court Decision, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Topical Correspondence: Lee Highway Vibration Problem, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Topical Correspondence: Schoolhouse, Kilmarnocic, Lancaster County (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Topical Correspondence: Spouse Abuse (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Topical Correspondence: Traffic Matters (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Constituent Letters [A], undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Letters [B], undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Letters: General, Answered, undated (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Constituent Letters and Non-Constituent Letters, Unanswered, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Series 2: Legislative Files, 1966-1992
  This series contains research for drafts and printed copies of legislation sponsored by or supported by Clive DuVal during service in the Virginia Senate, notably the Equal Rights Amendment, the Lottery Bill, nuclear regulation, public utility regulation, tax benefits for the elderly and handicapped, pesticide controls, beverage container law, mining industry regulation, transportation and highways, and higher education in Northern Virginia (Community College and George Mason University). Subseries 2.2 consists of studies on issues that are not necessarily linked to a specific bill. Such studies were used as background for developing a legislative agenda as well as for taking part in informed debate. Included in the studies are the major working files for the revision of the Virginia State Constitution (1968-1969) as well as information on such topics as the environment and nuclear energy regulation.
  - Subseries 2.1 - Congressional Bills, 1966-1992; (68 Boxes)
    This subseries contains drafts, notes, facsimiles, and research materials pertaining to specific bills sponsored or supported by Senator DuVal. The subseries is organized by date and alphabetically by subject or by bill number (e.g., HB0264, SB057, SB066, etc.) if available.
    - Twin Trailers, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Drug Substitution Bill, SB482, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Collection Agencies, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Restrictions on the Water Control Board (Gwathmey), HB0264, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Taxable Income, SB057, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Surface Mining of Minerals, SB066, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Strip Mining, SB072; SB074, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Workman's Compensation, SB093, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Legislation, SB110; SB111; SB112, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Motor Vehicles Law, SB127, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Suspension Chauffeurs Licenses, SB127, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Access to Government Meeting by Public, SB140, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Appointment of Non-Resident Fiduciaries, SB142, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Non-Resident Trustee Legislation, SB142, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Landlord-Tenant, SB168, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Landlord-Tenant, SB168; HB0220, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Containers, etc., SB174, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Containers, etc., SB174, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Oregon Beverage Container Bill, SB174, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - No Discrimination in the Extension of Credit, SB196, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Prohibit Discrimination Solely by Race, Color or Sex, SB196, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Costs, Fees, etc. to Sheriffs, SB207, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Falls Church Sheriff, SB207, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax $2,000 Exemption, SB231, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Employer Contributions to Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, SB232, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - VEA Increase Retirement Benefit, SB232, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Increase in Strip Mining Fees, SB271, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Relating to Surface Mining Permits, SB271, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Coal Mine Safety Provisions, SB272, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Deep mining Inspections, etc., SB272, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Refinancing Balloon Payments, SB5276, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Prohibition of Referral Transactions and Rights of Consumer, SB302, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Hearing v. Collections Agencies, SB311, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Licensing Persons Engaged in Selling Money Orders, SB330, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Money Order Licensing, SB330, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Requirement for Subdivision Plans (Brault), SB372, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Assessment and Taxation-Public Service Corp., SB394, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Assessed Valuation (Failed), SB394, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Assessments of Public Service Corporatic Property at Local Rate Rather [than] 40% (carried over), SB394, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Exemption - Rudolf Steiner School, SB407, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Exemption of Taxes, Rudolf Steiner School, SB407, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Changed by SCC, SB458, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Record on Appeal, State Corporation Commission, SB458, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Lobby Law, SB477, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Lobbying, SB477, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Decide Rezoning in 12 Months (Brault), SB490, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Powers of Transportation Districts, SB529, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Transportation Districts, SB529, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Purchase of Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Stores by Check, SB535, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Message Parlors and Technicians Regulations, SB642, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Late Filing for Relief by Elderly (may obtain 50% relief), SB733, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - License Tax Study, SJR033, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Proposed Amendment for ERA, SJR083, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Proposed Amendment for ERA, SJR096, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Balloon Payments, SJR276, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Capital Punishment, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - CLD Legislation, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Fair Trade, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County Historical Landmarks Preservation Commission Annual Report, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Scenic Rivers-Rivanna and Staunton "Virginia's Common Wealth,", 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - State Corporation Commission of Counties and Cities, HB0864, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Referral Bill, SB302, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Operation Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Stores, SB535, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Operation Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Stores, SB536, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Purchases at Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) Stores by Credit Card, SB536, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Pesticide Law, SB611, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Pesticide Application, SB611, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Newborn Children Insurance, SB612, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Newly Born Children Insurance Policies, SB612, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Pedlars (sic) License, SB614, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Tax on Peddlers, SB614, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Collection Agency Board (Receivership), SB617, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Funds Held by Collection Agents or Agencies, SB617, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Improve Thermal Design / VA Taxable Income, SB639, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - VA Taxable Income, SB639, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Regulations of Massage Therapy, SB642, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Expanding Membership, SCC, SB648, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Re: Membership State Corporation Commission, SB648, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Re: Exemptions from Hunting License Requirements, SB685, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Re: VA Taxable Income, SB705, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Retirees - Income Tax (and SB646), SB705, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Notice Before Termination of Utility Service, SB717, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Require Notice on Public Utility Service, SB717, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Re: Property Tax Relief for Elderly, SB733, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Emergency for Rate Making, SB743, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Re: Temporary Emergency Increase in Utility Taxation, SB743, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - National Wildlife Federation Exemption, SB758, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Property, Exemption State and Local Taxation, SB758, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Pesticide Law, SB787, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Pesticide Law (Housekeeping), SB787, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Debt Collection Policies Act, SB803, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Fair Debt Collection Practices Act, SB803, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Council on Physical Fitness, SB812, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Creating Virginia Common Physical Fitness, SB812, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Record Destruction (Fairfax Request), SB812, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - When Records May Be Destroyed, SB816, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Retail Sales and Use Taxes, SB824, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Sales Tax, Local Option (Fairfax / Arlington Request), SB824, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Retirees (Junkerman) Bill, SB827, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Taxable Income, SB827, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Appeals from Actions of State Corp. Commission, SB879, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - No Bond on Appeals from SCC, SB879, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Federal Rent Control, SB890, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Rent Control (Fairfax), SB890, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Conflict of Interest - Disclosure, SB893, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Resolution Re: Proration of Personal Property Tax on Cars Bought After January 1, SJR145, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Resources Study Assessment of [Personal Property], SJR145, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Directing DMV Study on Using Value of MV for Registration Fee, SJR147, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Resolution Re: Study of Placing Registration Fee on Value of Autos, SJR147, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - State Council of Higher Education Teacher Training, SJR149, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Study of Adequacy of Teacher Training, SJR149, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Resolution Study Re: Veterans' Credits for Service in Armed Forces and Homestead Exemptions, SJR152, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Study on Certain Veterans' Benefits, SJR152, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Beverage Container Legislation, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Beverage Container Legislation (pt 2), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Beverage Container Legislation (pt 3), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Bottle Bill, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Concorde SST (pt 1), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Concorde SST (pt 2), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Consumer Counsel and Consumer Congress, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Death With Dignity, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Drug Equivalent List-Drugs Used by the Aftercare Clinic, Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, Henrico Mental Hygiene Association, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - ERA, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Kepone 218, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Malpractice, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - PariMutuel Betting, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Pending Legislation, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Senate Finance Committee, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Upper Occoquan Sewage Plant, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Veterinary School, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Glasscock Posting of Drop Prices... of Drugs, HB0205, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Legislation 1976 now in Committee Amendment, HB0206 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Landlord-Tenant, HB0294, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Litter Tax Bill, HB0455, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Re: Malpractice Legislation, HB1212, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Brault Subcommittee, SB008, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Parimutuel Betting (Balabas) Re: Malpractice Legislation, SB010, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Falls Church City Charter (Amending of), SB022, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Special Assessments of Real Estate(ag., hort., for., etc.), SB039, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax-Comprehensive Plan "Environmental Area," SB041, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Zoning Ordinances Protection Against Degredation of Environmental Areas, SB041, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Prohibit Referral Transactions (Re: Consumer Sales/Leases), SB050, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Referral Transacting, SB050, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Beverage Container legislation, SB072, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Amendment Re: Limits on Amount of Loans Secured by Real Estate, SB108, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Loans Secured by Real Estate, SB108, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Creation of Form of Equivalent Drugs, SB109, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Generic Drug Bill, SB109, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Substitution of Prescription Drugs by Generic Name, Advertising SB109, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Increase Interest to 12% of Delinquent Property Taxes (Arlington), SB123, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Local Levies; Dates Filing Certain Returns, SB123, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Refundable Deposit Beverage Container Act (pt 1), SB132, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Refundable Deposit Beverage Container Act (pt 2), SB132, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Auto Insurance - Not to be Denied by Race, Sex, Age, etc., SB134, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Auto Liability Insurance (Howell Proposal), SB134, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Bank Appraisers (Holland), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Assessments for Local Improvements-Amendments Code, SB158, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Interest on Unfd. Enactment of Assessment (Arlington), SB158, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Eliminate Fuel Adjustment Clause, SB188, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Toxic Substance Act (pt 1), SB197, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Toxic Substance Act (pt 2), SB197, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Technical Amendments, Pesticide Law, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Pesticide Law, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Special Education for Handicapped Children (pt 1), SB209, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Special Education for Handicapped Children (pt 2), SB209, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Statewide Building Code (pt 1), SB217, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Statewide Building Code (pt 2), SB217, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Pesticide Law-Reg., 1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Retiree Legislation, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Special Hunting/Fishing License - Disabled Veterans, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Credit for Service in Armed Forces, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, SB373, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System; Service Armed Forces, SB373, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - VALC [Virginia Advisory Legislation Council] Finance (pt 1), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - VALC [Virginia Advisory Legislation Council] Finance (pt 2), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Absentee Ballots, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Absentee Ballots for Military, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Highway Transportation Commission, SB496, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Emergency Rate Increase, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Surface Mining of Minerals Other Than Coal (pt 1), SB510, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Surface Mining of Minerals Other Than Coal (pt 2), SB510, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Surface Mining of Minerals Other Than Coal (pt 3), SB510, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Amend Virginia Sales Tax, SB521, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Local Government Sales Tax, SB521, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Taxable Income, SB521, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - License to Hunt with Bow and Arrow (pt 1), SB539, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - License to Hunt with Bow and Arrow (pt 2), SB539, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - License to Hunt with a Bow and Arrow (pt 3), SB539, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - NOW in Committee amendment, SB218/SB548, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Boundary Line Between Alexandria and the City of Arlington, SB592, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Food and Beverage Tax, SB593, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Transient Occupancy Tax in Arlington County, SB594, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Wills of George and Martha Washington to Mt. Vernon, SB602, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Catoctin Creek State; Scenic Rivers Act, SB627, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Registration for Inspection of Vehicles, SB640, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Property Exemption from State and Local Tax, SB644, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Definitions Under the Homestead Act, SB658, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Provisions of Zoning Ordinances, SB671, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Taxation of Real Estate, SB689, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Discrimination in Issuance of Auto Insurance, SB691, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Voter Registration, Times and Places, SB716, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Bingo Games, Raffles, Penalties, SB728, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Taxation of Real Estate (Public Service Corporation), SB730, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Charges to Certain Customers for Electricity, SB731, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Removal of Children from Adoptive Home, SB732, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Northern Virginia Transportation District, Powers, Duties, SB479, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Solar Energy, SB762, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Add. Project and Fin., Authority for Small San. Districts, SB765, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Statewide Building Code, SB803, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Motor Vehicle Insurers to Provide Rate Statements, SB804, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Veterans Children Free Admission, SB805, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Committee to Nominate SCC Members, SB806, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Approp. Revenues, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Virginia Retail Sales and Use Tax, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Relief for Mauy Beach, SB847, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Discharge of Oil in State Waters, SB861, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Validate Contracts of Counties, etc. Re: Employment, SB872, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Virginia Suppl. Retirement System, SB882, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Ballots, SB886, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Amendment Re: Exemption from Property Taxation, SJR042, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Retirement of Charles Cecil Wall, SJR042, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Physical Abuse of Spouses, SJR089, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Auctioneers, SJR092, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Death of Violet Mac Dougall Pollard, SJR095, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Death of Major General Booth, SJR100, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ratify ERA, SJR111, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Non-Returnable Containers, SJR124, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Study of Fire Prevention Safety, Building Code, SJR127, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - SCC Study of Electric Utility Real Estate Holdings, SJR138, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Disclosure of Financial Records of Utility, SR26[0], 1976 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Scenic Rivers, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Voluntary Formula Revision, HB0205, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Cushman Claim, HB0588, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - San. - District (Arlington), HB0855, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Insurance Sales-Restrictions on Insurance Agents vs. Bakers, HB1144; SB626, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Annual Adjustment of Accelerated Sales Tax, Amendments to Budget Bill, SB090; SB105, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Subdivision Streets, SB105, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Fees May Be Paid for Bus Transportation, SB116, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Hearing in Divorce Matters by Commissioners, SB117, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Beverage Container Bill, SB193, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Setting Rates on Public Utilities by State Corp. Comm., SB375, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Residential Utility Consumer Group, SB509, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Landlord-Tenant (Holand), SB632, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Auto Inspection - County Sticker (Arlington), SB640, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Insurance - No Discrimination by Reason of Age, SB691, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Assessment Bill (Arlington), SB730, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Electricity Charges for Certain Customers, SB731, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Adoption - Judicial Review, SB732, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Sanitary District amendment, SB765, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)